<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>complex_decisions on theagile.company</title>
    <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/tags/complex_decisions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in complex_decisions on theagile.company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/tags/complex_decisions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Leverage collective intelligence with disciplined peer support</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/peer-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/peer-support/</guid>
      <description>Managers are facing similar challenges but in different realities: they use different solutions  The HR governance meeting was taking place six weeks after Maria was promoted HR director of the local subsidiary of a global software company. She was confronted with a major challenge: prepare a reorganization of some HR functions, with local HR headcount reduction, imposed by central HR. It was a rather effective action meeting: all agenda points of changes in roles/responsibilities between the different HR departments were covered quite rapidly with short-term actions, except one!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polarities: a systemic approach for business dilemma</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/polarities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/polarities/</guid>
      <description>Whenever we are confronted with conflicts around business dilemmas or complex challenges, one or more polarity(ies) could be the root cause(s). Some examples are:
 Centralized versus Decentralized Reduce cost versus Improve quality Compete versus Collaborate Take care of the organization versus Take care of the customer Deliberate strategy versus Emergent strategy Focus on task versus Focus on relationship Verify versus Trust Advocacy versus Inquiry  A polarity is composed of two opposites which do not function well independently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Structured self-management in business decision making: agile decisions</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/complex-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/complex-decisions/</guid>
      <description>Effective complex business decisions are threatened by many potential biases When it comes to (very) complex business decision making, we are not only confronted with the risk of ineffective interactions in meetings, but also with the risk of falling individually and collectively into different decision making biases. These biases are now well documented in the recent field of behavioral economics1. So it is also proven that the following subconscious biases do directly impact many, many business decisions2:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
