<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>You want more cooperation, agility and human growth in your organization. But progress is slow. on theagile.company</title>
    <link>https://s66erge.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in You want more cooperation, agility and human growth in your organization. But progress is slow. on theagile.company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://s66erge.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to improve present consciousness and individual agility</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/stop-rumination/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/stop-rumination/</guid>
      <description>High external pressure pushes us into rumination and stress, away from the present! Most of us assume that the events of life are causing stress. Particularly at work where employees say they have a stressful boss, stressful work, stressful timelines&amp;hellip;. But other employees in the same teams - with the same pressures - are not stressed out. So it&amp;rsquo;s not the event that causes stress.
To convert pressure into stress, you have to add an important intermediary step: rumination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Develop your leadership behaviors with the 360 listening/support process</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/listening-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/listening-support/</guid>
      <description>The objective of this process is to get a range of feedback about the leadership behaviors you could change and then get support from different people to help you effectively change the 1 or 2 most important behaviors you have selected.
There is clear statistical evidence over a population of more than 7,500 managers (see annex 2) that this whole process will trigger your successful leadership behavior changes if you meet your 6 to 8 colleagues once per month over a period of 6 months (see step 7)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How can we facilitate transformations with agile cooperation and human growth ?</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/leverage-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/leverage-points/</guid>
      <description>Modern change approaches integrate the human side, but success rate remains low \
Almost all change and/or transformation programs are based on the findings that collective effectiveness has become too low, usually against evolutions in the environment, and that a major cause is a combination of cooperation and collective agility.
And we all know that the traditional answer to this change imperative lead often to a vicious circle of stress, demotivation and disengagement:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join our 2016-17 program: Boost human growth and then business results</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/human-growth-program-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/human-growth-program-2016/</guid>
      <description>Why should you join? To cope with its more and more volatile, uncertain, complex and ambiguous (VUCA) reality, your organization needs people at every level to advance their human growth: contribute to more complex and wider business challenges
Your traditional hierarchical organization does not help enough to advance human growth. With great regularity, it
 limits individual initiative by imposing detailed controls and punishing mistakes constrains cooperation across departmental silos looks for short term simplistic trade-off between investments in human growth and business performance: then it loses on both sides!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016-11-08 Brussels: Co-create an agile company and human growth</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/event-20161108-brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/event-20161108-brussels/</guid>
      <description>Why did people like you join this workshop? The new Organization Workshop is for managers and employees working in organizations that are facing complex and rapidly changing environments and which need to evolve their management approach to increase cooperation, human growth and agility.
Based on a business simulation, this workshop has helped managers at forward thinking public and private sector organizations around the world experience:
 why traditional hierarchical organizations result in low cooperation and agility and little capacity to change how new work principles and practices can develop self-managing, cooperative and agile managers and employees  What was the reactions of participants?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016-10-13 Brussels: Co-create an agile company and human growth</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/event-20161013-brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/event-20161013-brussels/</guid>
      <description>Why did people like you join this workshop? The new Organization Workshop is for managers and employees working in organizations that are facing complex and rapidly changing environments and which need to evolve their management approach to increase cooperation, human growth and agility.
Based on a business simulation, this workshop has helped managers at forward thinking public and private sector organizations around the world experience:
 why traditional hierarchical organizations result in low cooperation and agility and little capacity to change how new work principles and practices can develop self-managing, cooperative and agile managers and employees  Here are video extracts of this workshop, including participant&amp;rsquo;s reactions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discovering through experience how organizations do shape our behaviors</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/ow-described/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/ow-described/</guid>
      <description>We are currently working on preparing this page content.
If you would like to influence our priorities so that we write this post more rapidly, please tell us so in the &amp;ldquo;Comment&amp;rdquo; box at the bottom of this post.
Thank you for your patience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to approach the implementation of the strategies?</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/implementation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/implementation/</guid>
      <description>It must be considered that there is nothing more difficult to carry out, nor more doubtful of success, nor more dangerous to handle, than to initiate a new order of things. For the reformer has enemies in all those who profit by the old order, and only lukewarm defenders in all those who would profit by the new order, &amp;hellip; Niccolo Machiavelli, ~1500AC.
 It is not a surprise that the failure rate of large business change management efforts has been high since the 80s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only widespread self-awareness can make traditional management systems sustainable</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/self-awareness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/self-awareness/</guid>
      <description>All power based hierarchies create these work contexts: Top/Middle/Bottom/Customer Traditional management systems are based on hierarchies with a large discretionary power of bosses over their (direct) reports. So our work experiences are influenced by our perception of the relationship with our direct boss.
 I vividly remember some periods of strong engagement when I was working for Jan or Eddie and the long periods of frustration and powerlessness when working for some of my other previous bosses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolve your collective agility with a culture of &#39;feedback loops&#39;</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/feedback-asking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/feedback-asking/</guid>
      <description>We are currently working on preparing this page content.
If you would like us to write this post more rapidly, please tell us so in the &amp;ldquo;Comment&amp;rdquo; box at the bottom of this post.
Thank you for your patience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How can we continuously develop self mastery?</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/self-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/self-development/</guid>
      <description>The foundation of a successful implementation of these strategiesleverage-points] is your own self-mastery, which I will define here as a the sum of these competencies:
 your systemic understanding of the (work) system around us your permanent inquiry of how we can better impact this (work) system your self-awareness, including the alignment of our actions with what we strive for  So how could you continuously develop your own self mastery?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leverage collective intelligence with disciplined peer support</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/peer-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/peer-support/</guid>
      <description>Managers are facing similar challenges but in different realities: they use different solutions  The HR governance meeting was taking place six weeks after Maria was promoted HR director of the local subsidiary of a global software company. She was confronted with a major challenge: prepare a reorganization of some HR functions, with local HR headcount reduction, imposed by central HR. It was a rather effective action meeting: all agenda points of changes in roles/responsibilities between the different HR departments were covered quite rapidly with short-term actions, except one!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polarities: a systemic approach for business dilemma</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/polarities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/polarities/</guid>
      <description>Whenever we are confronted with conflicts around business dilemmas or complex challenges, one or more polarity(ies) could be the root cause(s). Some examples are:
 Centralized versus Decentralized Reduce cost versus Improve quality Compete versus Collaborate Take care of the organization versus Take care of the customer Deliberate strategy versus Emergent strategy Focus on task versus Focus on relationship Verify versus Trust Advocacy versus Inquiry  A polarity is composed of two opposites which do not function well independently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Structured self-management in business decision making: agile decisions</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/complex-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/complex-decisions/</guid>
      <description>Effective complex business decisions are threatened by many potential biases When it comes to (very) complex business decision making, we are not only confronted with the risk of ineffective interactions in meetings, but also with the risk of falling individually and collectively into different decision making biases. These biases are now well documented in the recent field of behavioral economics1. So it is also proven that the following subconscious biases do directly impact many, many business decisions2:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Develop effective team behaviors with the feedforward process</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/feedforward/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/feedforward/</guid>
      <description>Fight silos by helping your team members to evolve their behaviors Henry, the head of the management team of the technology group of a worldwide IT company, was concerned about the mistrust between his team members and their silo mentality behaviors: they were always giving more priority to the results of their own departments, even at the expense of the overall results of the whole technology group.
Henry asked us to run 3 half-day team-building sessions to strengthen mutual trust and reduce the silo behavior of team members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016-05-17 Brussels: EXPERIENCE the emerging 21st century agile organization</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/event-20160517-brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/event-20160517-brussels/</guid>
      <description>During a 3-hour business simulation, you will experience organizational practices of agile companies like Zappos, W.L. Gore, Haier…
In this practical workshop, you will discover your answers to the following questions:
 Why are traditional hierarchical organizations creating resistance to change? How can leaders improve cooperation within their current organizations? Which management approaches are required for an agile 21st century organization?  This is the short version of a 1.5-day workshop which can help you accelerate a transformation in your company or organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/about-us/</guid>
      <description>Martine Bizouard My job is helping others to work better, be more agile and making change easier. I’ve done this with success for my clients for over 10 years now. These topics fully caught my attention when, as team manager on the trading floor of an international bank, I drove my team in the maelstrom of an nth merger depicted as a severe cultural choc. My primary concern was the individuals in my team, helping them leave the past and embrace the future, its new system with its new paradigm and mindset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact us</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>If you have found the resources on the site useful and would like to learn more about how we might be able to help you achieve your business goals, please contact us and we can have an informal chat to discuss your areas of interest.
Drop us a note to set up an initial phone discussion. We fully recognize that contacting a consultant/coach/facilitator can sometimes seem like a daunting prospect – but try us, we don’t bite!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disciplined self-management in meetings leads to agile action planning</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/action-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/action-meetings/</guid>
      <description>Lack of meeting structures creates weak decision making processes Few subjects do trigger a quasi unanimity in business and one of them is: meetings are too often a waste of time! Just observe your next meetings and you will rapidly see that the reality diverges frequently from generally accepted good practices:
   Good meeting practices Frequent meeting reality     participants remain on one subject until some agreed type of closure participants change subject before any apparent closure   group clarity on &amp;ldquo;diverging&amp;rdquo; (to brainstorm &amp;amp; share ideas) versus &amp;ldquo;converging&amp;rdquo; conversations unclear mix of &amp;ldquo;diverging&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;converging&amp;rdquo; (to take decisions) conversations   air time captured by one/few participant(s) air time actively distributed to everybody   almost every agenda item gets addressed many agenda items are delayed to next meeting(s)   everybody can speak without being interrupted interruptions do happen     Daniel, the Finance director of a large European country organization of a global software company, was looking at the yearly employee survey for his department.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you for joining us at this event / workshop</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/thank-you/</guid>
      <description>You will receive a confirmation email with the logistical details, 2 bonuses and a link to unregister if your agenda changes in the meantime.
The the agile.company team: Martine, Philippe, Guido et Serge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We are sorry that you cannot join us!</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/miss-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/miss-you/</guid>
      <description>We will miss you.
If you are not on our distribution list, do subscribe on the top right (or at the bottom on small screens) to receive our events and workshops announcements.
We hope to see you in one of our future workshops.
The the agile.company team: Martine, Philippe, Guido et Serge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy policy</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>This privacy policy sets out how Authentica uses and protects any information that you give to Authentica when you use this website.
Authentica is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Authentica may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/terms-of-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/terms-of-use/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our website. If you continue to browse and use this website, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern Authentica’s relationship with you in relation to this website. If you disagree with any part of these terms and conditions, please do not use our website.
The term ‘Authentica’ or ‘us’ or ‘we’ refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is: Authentica, 49 rue des trois ponts, 1160 Brussels, Belgium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Structured self-management is agility: BOTH creativity AND cooperation</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/disciplined-autonomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/disciplined-autonomy/</guid>
      <description>Using hierarchical control for alignment &amp;amp; collaboration is killing creativity Since they exist, almost all companies are using hierarchical control to ensure alignment and collaboration. The same companies need also creative employees at every level in order to thrive or just to survive! We know that self-management is the first and most important driver of human engagement and creativity: this has been proven since the 80s in psychology research1 and in real companies2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/zfoot1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/zfoot1/</guid>
      <description>Who are we? We are a team of coaches / facilitators / consultants known for our expertise in helping leaders to evolve management behaviors and practices that enable true business transformation.
We have helped large companies active in Europe to successfully adapt their management practices, impacting a few hundred to a few thousand people, among others: AXA, Belgacom, BNP Paribas, Carrefour, Engie (Suez and Electrabel), GlaxoSmithKline, Groupe Rocher, Guinness, L’Oréal, Mazars, Microsoft, Pfizer, Safran, Société Générale, Snecma…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/zfoot2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/zfoot2/</guid>
      <description>What do we bring you? We have made it our mission to help managers, like yourself, who passionately want to create agile companies in which people grow and develop.
We help you achieve results fast. First you will get the satisfaction from seeing your people flourish. Then you will receive the recognition for a sustainably improved business performance.
Most importantly, our clients change their management practices and culture and succeed their business transformation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/zfoot3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/zfoot3/</guid>
      <description>How do we help you? Specifically, we
 challenge managers into visibly ‘walking the transformation talk&#39; offer consistent, flexible and adaptive frameworks for effectively making agile decisions and permanently adapting roles/responsibilities to outside solutions help extend the scope of responsibilities of managers and employees, within that framework, to become more committed and self-directing.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
