<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>structure on theagile.company</title>
    <link>https://s66erge.github.io/tags/structure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in structure on theagile.company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://s66erge.github.io/tags/structure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Disciplined self-management in meetings leads to agile action planning</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/action-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/action-meetings/</guid>
      <description>Lack of meeting structures creates weak decision making processes Few subjects do trigger a quasi unanimity in business and one of them is: meetings are too often a waste of time! Just observe your next meetings and you will rapidly see that the reality diverges frequently from generally accepted good practices:
   Good meeting practices Frequent meeting reality     participants remain on one subject until some agreed type of closure participants change subject before any apparent closure   group clarity on &amp;ldquo;diverging&amp;rdquo; (to brainstorm &amp;amp; share ideas) versus &amp;ldquo;converging&amp;rdquo; conversations unclear mix of &amp;ldquo;diverging&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;converging&amp;rdquo; (to take decisions) conversations   air time captured by one/few participant(s) air time actively distributed to everybody   almost every agenda item gets addressed many agenda items are delayed to next meeting(s)   everybody can speak without being interrupted interruptions do happen     Daniel, the Finance director of a large European country organization of a global software company, was looking at the yearly employee survey for his department.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Structured self-management is agility: BOTH creativity AND cooperation</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/disciplined-autonomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/disciplined-autonomy/</guid>
      <description>Using hierarchical control for alignment &amp;amp; collaboration is killing creativity Since they exist, almost all companies are using hierarchical control to ensure alignment and collaboration. The same companies need also creative employees at every level in order to thrive or just to survive! We know that self-management is the first and most important driver of human engagement and creativity: this has been proven since the 80s in psychology research1 and in real companies2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
