<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>decision_meeting on theagile.company</title>
    <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/tags/decision_meeting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in decision_meeting on theagile.company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/tags/decision_meeting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2016-11-08 Brussels: Co-create an agile company and human growth</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/workshop/event-20161108-brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/workshop/event-20161108-brussels/</guid>
      <description>Why did people like you join this workshop? The new Organization Workshop is for managers and employees working in organizations that are facing complex and rapidly changing environments and which need to evolve their management approach to increase cooperation, human growth and agility.
Based on a business simulation, this workshop has helped managers at forward thinking public and private sector organizations around the world experience:
 why traditional hierarchical organizations result in low cooperation and agility and little capacity to change how new work principles and practices can develop self-managing, cooperative and agile managers and employees  What was the reactions of participants?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016-10-13 Brussels: Co-create an agile company and human growth</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/workshop/event-20161013-brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/workshop/event-20161013-brussels/</guid>
      <description>Why did people like you join this workshop? The new Organization Workshop is for managers and employees working in organizations that are facing complex and rapidly changing environments and which need to evolve their management approach to increase cooperation, human growth and agility.
Based on a business simulation, this workshop has helped managers at forward thinking public and private sector organizations around the world experience:
 why traditional hierarchical organizations result in low cooperation and agility and little capacity to change how new work principles and practices can develop self-managing, cooperative and agile managers and employees  Here are video extracts of this workshop, including participant&amp;rsquo;s reactions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Structured self-management in business decision making: agile decisions</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/complex-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/complex-decisions/</guid>
      <description>Effective complex business decisions are threatened by many potential biases When it comes to (very) complex business decision making, we are not only confronted with the risk of ineffective interactions in meetings, but also with the risk of falling individually and collectively into different decision making biases. These biases are now well documented in the recent field of behavioral economics1. So it is also proven that the following subconscious biases do directly impact many, many business decisions2:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016-05-17 Brussels: EXPERIENCE the emerging 21st century agile organization</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/workshop/event-20160517-brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/workshop/event-20160517-brussels/</guid>
      <description>During a 3-hour business simulation, you will experience organizational practices of agile companies like Zappos, W.L. Gore, Haier…
In this practical workshop, you will discover your answers to the following questions:
 Why are traditional hierarchical organizations creating resistance to change? How can leaders improve cooperation within their current organizations? Which management approaches are required for an agile 21st century organization?  This is the short version of a 1.5-day workshop which can help you accelerate a transformation in your company or organization.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
