<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>leading_by_example on theagile.company</title>
    <link>https://s66erge.github.io/tags/leading_by_example/</link>
    <description>Recent content in leading_by_example on theagile.company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://s66erge.github.io/tags/leading_by_example/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Join our 2016-17 program: Boost human growth and then business results</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/human-growth-program-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/human-growth-program-2016/</guid>
      <description>Why should you join? To cope with its more and more volatile, uncertain, complex and ambiguous (VUCA) reality, your organization needs people at every level to advance their human growth: contribute to more complex and wider business challenges
Your traditional hierarchical organization does not help enough to advance human growth. With great regularity, it
 limits individual initiative by imposing detailed controls and punishing mistakes constrains cooperation across departmental silos looks for short term simplistic trade-off between investments in human growth and business performance: then it loses on both sides!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to approach the implementation of the strategies?</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/implementation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/implementation/</guid>
      <description>It must be considered that there is nothing more difficult to carry out, nor more doubtful of success, nor more dangerous to handle, than to initiate a new order of things. For the reformer has enemies in all those who profit by the old order, and only lukewarm defenders in all those who would profit by the new order, &amp;hellip; Niccolo Machiavelli, ~1500AC.
 It is not a surprise that the failure rate of large business change management efforts has been high since the 80s.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
