<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>self-management on theagile.company</title>
    <link>https://s66erge.github.io/tags/self-management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in self-management on theagile.company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://s66erge.github.io/tags/self-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How can we facilitate transformations with agile cooperation and human growth ?</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/leverage-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/leverage-points/</guid>
      <description>Modern change approaches integrate the human side, but success rate remains low \
Almost all change and/or transformation programs are based on the findings that collective effectiveness has become too low, usually against evolutions in the environment, and that a major cause is a combination of cooperation and collective agility.
And we all know that the traditional answer to this change imperative lead often to a vicious circle of stress, demotivation and disengagement:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016-11-08 Brussels: Co-create an agile company and human growth</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/event-20161108-brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/event-20161108-brussels/</guid>
      <description>Why did people like you join this workshop? The new Organization Workshop is for managers and employees working in organizations that are facing complex and rapidly changing environments and which need to evolve their management approach to increase cooperation, human growth and agility.
Based on a business simulation, this workshop has helped managers at forward thinking public and private sector organizations around the world experience:
 why traditional hierarchical organizations result in low cooperation and agility and little capacity to change how new work principles and practices can develop self-managing, cooperative and agile managers and employees  What was the reactions of participants?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016-10-13 Brussels: Co-create an agile company and human growth</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/event-20161013-brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/event-20161013-brussels/</guid>
      <description>Why did people like you join this workshop? The new Organization Workshop is for managers and employees working in organizations that are facing complex and rapidly changing environments and which need to evolve their management approach to increase cooperation, human growth and agility.
Based on a business simulation, this workshop has helped managers at forward thinking public and private sector organizations around the world experience:
 why traditional hierarchical organizations result in low cooperation and agility and little capacity to change how new work principles and practices can develop self-managing, cooperative and agile managers and employees  Here are video extracts of this workshop, including participant&amp;rsquo;s reactions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Structured self-management in business decision making: agile decisions</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/complex-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/complex-decisions/</guid>
      <description>Effective complex business decisions are threatened by many potential biases When it comes to (very) complex business decision making, we are not only confronted with the risk of ineffective interactions in meetings, but also with the risk of falling individually and collectively into different decision making biases. These biases are now well documented in the recent field of behavioral economics1. So it is also proven that the following subconscious biases do directly impact many, many business decisions2:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016-05-17 Brussels: EXPERIENCE the emerging 21st century agile organization</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/event-20160517-brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/workshop/event-20160517-brussels/</guid>
      <description>During a 3-hour business simulation, you will experience organizational practices of agile companies like Zappos, W.L. Gore, Haier…
In this practical workshop, you will discover your answers to the following questions:
 Why are traditional hierarchical organizations creating resistance to change? How can leaders improve cooperation within their current organizations? Which management approaches are required for an agile 21st century organization?  This is the short version of a 1.5-day workshop which can help you accelerate a transformation in your company or organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disciplined self-management in meetings leads to agile action planning</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/action-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/action-meetings/</guid>
      <description>Lack of meeting structures creates weak decision making processes Few subjects do trigger a quasi unanimity in business and one of them is: meetings are too often a waste of time! Just observe your next meetings and you will rapidly see that the reality diverges frequently from generally accepted good practices:
   Good meeting practices Frequent meeting reality     participants remain on one subject until some agreed type of closure participants change subject before any apparent closure   group clarity on &amp;ldquo;diverging&amp;rdquo; (to brainstorm &amp;amp; share ideas) versus &amp;ldquo;converging&amp;rdquo; conversations unclear mix of &amp;ldquo;diverging&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;converging&amp;rdquo; (to take decisions) conversations   air time captured by one/few participant(s) air time actively distributed to everybody   almost every agenda item gets addressed many agenda items are delayed to next meeting(s)   everybody can speak without being interrupted interruptions do happen     Daniel, the Finance director of a large European country organization of a global software company, was looking at the yearly employee survey for his department.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Structured self-management is agility: BOTH creativity AND cooperation</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/post/disciplined-autonomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/post/disciplined-autonomy/</guid>
      <description>Using hierarchical control for alignment &amp;amp; collaboration is killing creativity Since they exist, almost all companies are using hierarchical control to ensure alignment and collaboration. The same companies need also creative employees at every level in order to thrive or just to survive! We know that self-management is the first and most important driver of human engagement and creativity: this has been proven since the 80s in psychology research1 and in real companies2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
