<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cooperation on theagile.company</title>
    <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/tags/cooperation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cooperation on theagile.company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/tags/cooperation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How can we facilitate transformations with agile cooperation and human growth ?</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/leverage-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/leverage-points/</guid>
      <description>Modern change approaches integrate the human side, but success rate remains low \
Almost all change and/or transformation programs are based on the findings that collective effectiveness has become too low, usually against evolutions in the environment, and that a major cause is a combination of cooperation and collective agility.
And we all know that the traditional answer to this change imperative lead often to a vicious circle of stress, demotivation and disengagement:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join our 2016-17 program: Boost human growth and then business results</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/workshop/human-growth-program-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/workshop/human-growth-program-2016/</guid>
      <description>Why should you join? To cope with its more and more volatile, uncertain, complex and ambiguous (VUCA) reality, your organization needs people at every level to advance their human growth: contribute to more complex and wider business challenges
Your traditional hierarchical organization does not help enough to advance human growth. With great regularity, it
 limits individual initiative by imposing detailed controls and punishing mistakes constrains cooperation across departmental silos looks for short term simplistic trade-off between investments in human growth and business performance: then it loses on both sides!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016-11-08 Brussels: Co-create an agile company and human growth</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/workshop/event-20161108-brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/workshop/event-20161108-brussels/</guid>
      <description>Why did people like you join this workshop? The new Organization Workshop is for managers and employees working in organizations that are facing complex and rapidly changing environments and which need to evolve their management approach to increase cooperation, human growth and agility.
Based on a business simulation, this workshop has helped managers at forward thinking public and private sector organizations around the world experience:
 why traditional hierarchical organizations result in low cooperation and agility and little capacity to change how new work principles and practices can develop self-managing, cooperative and agile managers and employees  What was the reactions of participants?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016-10-13 Brussels: Co-create an agile company and human growth</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/workshop/event-20161013-brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/workshop/event-20161013-brussels/</guid>
      <description>Why did people like you join this workshop? The new Organization Workshop is for managers and employees working in organizations that are facing complex and rapidly changing environments and which need to evolve their management approach to increase cooperation, human growth and agility.
Based on a business simulation, this workshop has helped managers at forward thinking public and private sector organizations around the world experience:
 why traditional hierarchical organizations result in low cooperation and agility and little capacity to change how new work principles and practices can develop self-managing, cooperative and agile managers and employees  Here are video extracts of this workshop, including participant&amp;rsquo;s reactions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016-05-17 Brussels: EXPERIENCE the emerging 21st century agile organization</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/workshop/event-20160517-brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/workshop/event-20160517-brussels/</guid>
      <description>During a 3-hour business simulation, you will experience organizational practices of agile companies like Zappos, W.L. Gore, Haier…
In this practical workshop, you will discover your answers to the following questions:
 Why are traditional hierarchical organizations creating resistance to change? How can leaders improve cooperation within their current organizations? Which management approaches are required for an agile 21st century organization?  This is the short version of a 1.5-day workshop which can help you accelerate a transformation in your company or organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disciplined self-management in meetings leads to agile action planning</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/action-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/action-meetings/</guid>
      <description>Lack of meeting structures creates weak decision making processes Few subjects do trigger a quasi unanimity in business and one of them is: meetings are too often a waste of time! Just observe your next meetings and you will rapidly see that the reality diverges frequently from generally accepted good practices:
   Good meeting practices Frequent meeting reality     participants remain on one subject until some agreed type of closure participants change subject before any apparent closure   group clarity on &amp;ldquo;diverging&amp;rdquo; (to brainstorm &amp;amp; share ideas) versus &amp;ldquo;converging&amp;rdquo; conversations unclear mix of &amp;ldquo;diverging&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;converging&amp;rdquo; (to take decisions) conversations   air time captured by one/few participant(s) air time actively distributed to everybody   almost every agenda item gets addressed many agenda items are delayed to next meeting(s)   everybody can speak without being interrupted interruptions do happen     Daniel, the Finance director of a large European country organization of a global software company, was looking at the yearly employee survey for his department.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
