<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on theagile.company</title>
    <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on theagile.company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://s66erge.github.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/about-us/</guid>
      <description>Martine Bizouard My job is helping others to work better, be more agile and making change easier. I’ve done this with success for my clients for over 10 years now. These topics fully caught my attention when, as team manager on the trading floor of an international bank, I drove my team in the maelstrom of an nth merger depicted as a severe cultural choc. My primary concern was the individuals in my team, helping them leave the past and embrace the future, its new system with its new paradigm and mindset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact us</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>If you have found the resources on the site useful and would like to learn more about how we might be able to help you achieve your business goals, please contact us and we can have an informal chat to discuss your areas of interest.
Drop us a note to set up an initial phone discussion. We fully recognize that contacting a consultant/coach/facilitator can sometimes seem like a daunting prospect – but try us, we don’t bite!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you for joining us at this event / workshop</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/thank-you/</guid>
      <description>You will receive a confirmation email with the logistical details, 2 bonuses and a link to unregister if your agenda changes in the meantime.
The the agile.company team: Martine, Philippe, Guido et Serge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We are sorry that you cannot join us!</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/miss-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/miss-you/</guid>
      <description>We will miss you.
If you are not on our distribution list, do subscribe on the top right (or at the bottom on small screens) to receive our events and workshops announcements.
We hope to see you in one of our future workshops.
The the agile.company team: Martine, Philippe, Guido et Serge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy policy</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>This privacy policy sets out how Authentica uses and protects any information that you give to Authentica when you use this website.
Authentica is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Authentica may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/terms-of-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/terms-of-use/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our website. If you continue to browse and use this website, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern Authentica’s relationship with you in relation to this website. If you disagree with any part of these terms and conditions, please do not use our website.
The term ‘Authentica’ or ‘us’ or ‘we’ refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is: Authentica, 49 rue des trois ponts, 1160 Brussels, Belgium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/zfoot1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/zfoot1/</guid>
      <description>Who are we? We are a team of coaches / facilitators / consultants known for our expertise in helping leaders to evolve management behaviors and practices that enable true business transformation.
We have helped large companies active in Europe to successfully adapt their management practices, impacting a few hundred to a few thousand people, among others: AXA, Belgacom, BNP Paribas, Carrefour, Engie (Suez and Electrabel), GlaxoSmithKline, Groupe Rocher, Guinness, L’Oréal, Mazars, Microsoft, Pfizer, Safran, Société Générale, Snecma…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/zfoot2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/zfoot2/</guid>
      <description>What do we bring you? We have made it our mission to help managers, like yourself, who passionately want to create agile companies in which people grow and develop.
We help you achieve results fast. First you will get the satisfaction from seeing your people flourish. Then you will receive the recognition for a sustainably improved business performance.
Most importantly, our clients change their management practices and culture and succeed their business transformation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/page/zfoot3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/page/zfoot3/</guid>
      <description>How do we help you? Specifically, we
 challenge managers into visibly ‘walking the transformation talk&#39; offer consistent, flexible and adaptive frameworks for effectively making agile decisions and permanently adapting roles/responsibilities to outside solutions help extend the scope of responsibilities of managers and employees, within that framework, to become more committed and self-directing.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
