<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>foundation on theagile.company</title>
    <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/categories/foundation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in foundation on theagile.company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/categories/foundation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How can we facilitate transformations with agile cooperation and human growth ?</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/leverage-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/leverage-points/</guid>
      <description>Modern change approaches integrate the human side, but success rate remains low \
Almost all change and/or transformation programs are based on the findings that collective effectiveness has become too low, usually against evolutions in the environment, and that a major cause is a combination of cooperation and collective agility.
And we all know that the traditional answer to this change imperative lead often to a vicious circle of stress, demotivation and disengagement:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to approach the implementation of the strategies?</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/implementation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/implementation/</guid>
      <description>It must be considered that there is nothing more difficult to carry out, nor more doubtful of success, nor more dangerous to handle, than to initiate a new order of things. For the reformer has enemies in all those who profit by the old order, and only lukewarm defenders in all those who would profit by the new order, &amp;hellip; Niccolo Machiavelli, ~1500AC.
 It is not a surprise that the failure rate of large business change management efforts has been high since the 80s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only widespread self-awareness can make traditional management systems sustainable</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/self-awareness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/self-awareness/</guid>
      <description>All power based hierarchies create these work contexts: Top/Middle/Bottom/Customer Traditional management systems are based on hierarchies with a large discretionary power of bosses over their (direct) reports. So our work experiences are influenced by our perception of the relationship with our direct boss.
 I vividly remember some periods of strong engagement when I was working for Jan or Eddie and the long periods of frustration and powerlessness when working for some of my other previous bosses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How can we continuously develop self mastery?</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/self-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/self-development/</guid>
      <description>The foundation of a successful implementation of these strategiesleverage-points] is your own self-mastery, which I will define here as a the sum of these competencies:
 your systemic understanding of the (work) system around us your permanent inquiry of how we can better impact this (work) system your self-awareness, including the alignment of our actions with what we strive for  So how could you continuously develop your own self mastery?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polarities: a systemic approach for business dilemma</title>
      <link>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/polarities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s66erge.github.io/theagilecompany/post/polarities/</guid>
      <description>Whenever we are confronted with conflicts around business dilemmas or complex challenges, one or more polarity(ies) could be the root cause(s). Some examples are:
 Centralized versus Decentralized Reduce cost versus Improve quality Compete versus Collaborate Take care of the organization versus Take care of the customer Deliberate strategy versus Emergent strategy Focus on task versus Focus on relationship Verify versus Trust Advocacy versus Inquiry  A polarity is composed of two opposites which do not function well independently.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
